technicolor.com 2006-06-19

# TECHNICOLOR - PRIVACY POLICY

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Protecting an individual's privacy is at the core of what we do at Technicolor, a subsidiary of Thomson, and is a critical component of the services that we offer.

We have internal policies and guidelines in place to protect the privacy of the information we have about our individual consumers. We are continually working to find new and better ways to maximize the privacy and security of this information when servicing our customers.

**Your Privacy Is Important To Us!**

We, at Thomson, value your trust and confidence.

We believe that we earn your trust and confidence when we continue to bring you exceptional products or services for your digital home and do so in a very private and secure manner. We believe that trust and confidence is sustained as we honor that commitment to you, day in and day out.

Thomson is a global company, offering digital products and services worldwide for your home, with brands such as THOMSON and RCA. This privacy statement is applicable to the information we collect on our websites.

We created this privacy statement to inform you of our global commitment to you.

**Keeping Your Information Secure**

Keeping the personal information we collect about you secure is one of our most important responsibilities. We value your trust and handle personal information with care. Our employees access information about you when needed to complete your product purchase, maintain your service or warranty agreements and otherwise meet your needs. We may also access information about you when considering a request from you for additional services, honoring our agreement with you or when responding to requests as required by law.

We safeguard information according to established security standards and procedures, and we continually assess new technology for protecting information. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles.

**Working to meet your needs through information.** In the course of doing business, we collect and use various types of information, such as information available from public records and market research, as well as information you provide to us. We use this information to serve you and to help you learn more about home digital products. 

**We collect personally identifiable information from you** , for example, when you purchase a product or service contract, when you register on one of our websites, complete a survey, or when you request information from one of our family of companies.

The personal information we collect includes, for example, name, address, preferences, credit card information to process purchases, e-mail addresses, click stream and navigation data. 

**Keeping Information Accurate**

Keeping personal information accurate and up-to-date is very important. Our customer service personnel are available to review the information we hold about you, such as your warranties and service contracts, so that together we can confirm their accuracy. If you ever find that information about you is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, we want to correct it. Please contact us through one of the contact mechanisms listed below.

**We Bring You Value And Benefits, While Honoring Your Preferences**

When we accept your personal information we use it to provide you goods and services, establish warranties and service contracts and to provide you quality customer services. 

**How-And-Why Information Is Shared**

> We limit who receives information and what type of information is shared. We share information with the goal of bringing you innovative digital products and more choices.
> 
> **_Sharing information within Thomson._** To offer you a full suite of Thomson digital home goods and services, the personal information we have about you may be shared among the family of Thomson companies as permitted by law and our agreement with you.
> 
> **_Sharing information with companies that work for us._** To assist us in offering you goods and services, we may occasionally share information with companies that work for us, such as companies that process your order or record your warranty information.
> 
> _**Sharing information with companies that bring you value.**_ Personal information excluding credit card information may be shared with other reputable organizations whose products and services you may find beneficial. 
> 
> **_Sharing information with others._** We may provide your information as required by law or legal process; to protect and defend the rights of Thomson and under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users, Thomson, this site, or the public.

**Offering You Choices**

You will be offered an opportunity to express your preference regarding the use and dissemination of information about you. That opportunity may be made available at the time you register on our website or when you fill out a warranty card. You may always call our customer service units or contact us using the information listed below to share your preferences with us. While the specific preferences offered may vary from region to region across the world due to local law and/or practice, it is Thomson's goal to listen and honor our customers' preferences. Your continued trust and confidence depends upon it.

**Other Sites**

Thomson websites may contain links to other sites; however, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by the other sites. We encourage you to read these other privacy statements.

**Effective Date**

This policy is effective January 1, 2001. We may make and post changes to this statement in an effort to ensure you are clearly informed of any changes in our information handling practices.

**Ask Us**

If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, you can contact us at the following email address: [privacy@thomson.net]. Your e-mail address will be added to the personally identifiable information we collect from you.

If you would like to contact us via phone or mail, please call or write us at:

Europe  
THOMSON (Headquarters)  
46 Quai Alphonse Le Gallo   
926 BOULOGNE cedex  
TEL : 33 (0)1 41 86 50 00  
Americas   
Thomson (formerly Thomson Consumer Electronics, Inc.)  
Americas Customer Service Center  
7225 Winton Drive, PO Box 1976  
Indianapolis, IN 46268  
TEL : (1 317) 415 3900  
Asia  
THOMSON ASIA Pte Ltd  
8 Jurong Town Hall Road #30-01/06  
609434 SINGAPORE  
TEL : (65) 379 1300
